and we're excited to have you here in
the Carolinas.
>> We're going to kick things off with
Cassidy Hill.
>> Hey, Will. How's it going?
>> It's going good. It's going good. How
you doing?
>> I'm doing good. Probably not as as good
as you right now. I imagine it's an
exciting day.
>> Yeah.
>> Um, quick, I I have a feeling I know
where this is going, but just curious,
can you tell me how you got the nickname
the blanket and and who first gave you
that?
>> Yeah. When I was uh in junior college. I
was in junior college and uh I went on
like my first my first three games
playing there. I I had like zero targets
the first three games and my teammates
were in like we were in lunch. My
teammates were basically saying like you
locking people up like a blanket out
there like it's crazy. And then my DB
coach heard about it and he was like we
was making jokes saying it was corny and
then few weeks later I was like man this
really stick like I might take it and
run with it like it's fire. So I ended
up taking it and running with it in JO
and made it a big thing.
Did you ever look into that as like an
NIL deal like uh repping blankets or
anything?
>> Yeah. Yeah. I didn't had a few blanket
companies reach out to me and you know
we trying to get stuff situated but when
I was in uh college uh I used to do
things like give blankets to charities
and stuff like that so before like in
away games. So yeah, I started doing
little things like that but I'm ready to
uh take off with it.
>> That's awesome. One other quick one for
me. Tell me what it's like being the
youngest with six older sisters. Uh,
it's crazy, you know. Um, what's really
what's really crazy about it, they're on
my mom's side, so, you know, they're
older now, so they're really grown, but
they reach out and see me doing all the
football things and like my nieces and
nephews, they see me play, and they they
be like sending videos of them playing
football and stuff, and they they look
up to me. So, it's a it's crazy. It's a
big thing, though.
>> That's awesome. Thanks so much.
Congratul
>> Yeah. Thank you,
>> Joe. Person.
>> Hey, Will. Congrats, man. Thank you.
>> Did um do do you have uh an idea? Have
the Panthers told you kind of how they
view you? I mean, are I know you
primarily an outside guy, but uh are
they thinking all that they might use
you in the slot as well?
>> Uh they they really haven't told me
anything specific, but you know, I'm
willing to, you know, play anywhere. You
know, anything to help the defense and
help the team succeed. I could be an
outside guy, could be a slot guy, and
even if I got to get moved to safety, I
can make that happen. So, you know, I'm
just willing to do anything to help the
team. I'm excited. You know, I'm ready
to I'm ready to put in that work.
>> What do you think your best attributes
are?
>> Uh my press man. You know, I feel like I
was the best press man quarterback in
the uh in the draft. And you know, you
know, God had different plans. I ended
up falling later than I thought, but you
know, I'm ready to showcase my talent
and showcase them. I'm the best press
man quarterback in the uh in the draft.
>> As you know, man, you play a position
where you're on an island, especially in
press man. I know you gave up some deep
balls this year. How how big was that in
terms of just moving on to the next
player. How how did you handle those uh
those adversity that those adversities?
>> Uh you know just having a forgetful
mindset, you know, one play, next play,
you know, you got to forget about it.
You know, you got to you got to have a
forgetful mindset. And you know, this
game that we play, a lot of guys play it
at a high level and you're not the only
guy out there that's trying to succeed.
So, you know, good guys are going to
make good plays and you got to live with
it. and you just got to have a forgetful
mindset and go out there and and you
know play the next down.
>> Thanks a lot.
>> Yeah, thank you.
>> We'll go with my K followed by Alex.
>> Hey Will, welcome. Uh unfortunately I
got on here a little late so if I'm
asking a a repeat question I apologize
but obviously you were well traveled
during your college career. How much did
that prepare you in learning different
schemes and different coverage shells
and just kind of adapting to new
environments?
>> Yeah. Um, you know, it it made my my
thinking of the game really broad. You
know, uh, being at Kansas State, you
know, we was a real heavy board team.
You know, we learned a lot of our
defense on the whiteboard. And then
coming to uh Texas A&M with Coach Elco,
he has a more of a NFL style defense.
You know, we do a lot of walkthroughs.
So, it kind of made me versatile in my
learning habits. So, it made me pick up
learning habits easier to make me, you
know, learn the playbooks faster and,
you know, get ahead of that.
Did you get to meet with Jonathan Kulie
or EJ before during the process? I'm
sorry if you were asked that already.
And obviously, you know, they work in a
lot of shell coverage that they're in
zone. I know you said you love being a
press man, but how do you feel about
being in space and and protecting an
area?
>> Uh, yeah, I'm real comfortable with
that. You know, with Coach Elco's
defense, we had a lot of, you know, we
had a lot of hybrid defenses where, you
know, we' be man to the boundary, zone
to the field or flip-flop, reverse. So,
we had a lot of that in our uh playbook.
And then being at Kansas State, we
played a lot of quarters. So, you know,
I was real used to playing quarters at
Kansas State. So, I'm really comfortable
playing anywhere. But my strong suit,
you know, I feel like I'm a real top
tier man quarterback. But I'm
comfortable playing anywhere.
>> Have you heard from Nick Gordon yet?
>> No, I saw him post. He tagged me in an
Instagram post saying, "Congrats." And
he ready to put in that work. But, you
know, I'm glad to be back with my dog.
You feel me? That's it's really
exciting.
>> Congratulations.
>> Yeah. Thank you. Any more questions for
Will?
>> Okay.
>> Hi. Uh, congratulations. You're going to
be in a cornerback room with JC Horn and
Mike Jack. I'm just curious your
familiarity with those guys.
>> Yeah. Uh, with JC Horn, I've been
watching them since I was in junior
college. You know, um, he had videos out
there with Oliver Davis, his trainer
that they used to post on YouTube, and
I've been watching it forever. And you
know, I always told I always told my
friends and everything like JC Horn, one
of my favorite quarterbacks to play
with. So now, you know, coming in there
and being the Carolina Panthers, you
know, just having him as that leader,
you know, that that vet and you can, you
know, take his shadow and watch how he
works, you know, it's a great thing to
have just being able to watch his game
previously before I got here.
>> Thanks.
>> Yeah,
>> we'll go with Cassidy Hill.
>> Hey, sorry. Yeah, let me get this back
on. Um will how much did your basketball
and baseball background kind of help you
as you
developed into a corner?
>> Yeah. um you know just you know playing
basketball you know just the simple
things you know playing defense and just
moving your feet in that aspect and just
having good h uh hip fluidity you know
that's a big thing and just you know
playing basketball just being more
flexible you know being more nimble you
know I feel like you play one sport you
kind of get stiff you know guys that can
play multiple sports and do a lot of
different things you be flexible in your
body so playing basketball and baseball
was real fun
>> we have time for a couple more we'll go
back to bash
You mentioned that you got picked lower
than you expected. I'm just curious what
these last few days have been like for
you.
>> Uh it's been humbling. You know, it's
been a humbling experience, but you
know, like a guy like me coming from St.
Louis, Missouri and then, you know,
being a JO product, you know, it's
nothing I wasn't expecting and I wasn't
built for, you know. Um, you know, it's
a real humbling experience, but you
know, with me, like I got a hard skin,
so I was ready. So, whatever team that
got me, they going to give my all, you
know, I'm going to show it.
>> Does it make the chip on your shoulder
even bigger? Yeah, even bigger. You
know, I always felt like I had to work
harder than everybody else to get to
where I wanted to go. So, I'm ready for
it. It's nothing new. I've been doing
this my whole life. I'm ready.
>> Thanks.
>> Yeah.
>> All right. Well, that looks like all the
questions we have for you this
afternoon. And we thank you so much for
taking the time to talk to us.
>> Yeah. Thank you so much.
>> Once again, congratulations and welcome
to the Carolinas.
>> Yep. Thank you. I appreciate it.